ANDRES RAMIREZ

WEB DEV

amirezsilva@gmail.com

.....o_o....

San Jose, Costa Rica

C.

+506 87416679



https://jabali04.github.io/portfolio/

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT - PLAZI 2021-Present.

SYSTEMS ENGINEERING- UNED 2022-Present.

CCNA - CICAP 2019

LPIC-1 - LINUX ACADEMY 2021

FRONT-END SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT
- SQL
- NODE JS
- C#
- PYTHON

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native English: Advanced

PROFILE

Web developer passionate about frontend technologies. I enjoy the creative possibilities that front-end development allows us, as well as the understanding of the artistic and conceptual currents that influence this technological area.

Additionally, I have a vast experience in IT (Linux, networking and security) which adds value in understanding the general structure of a web application.

EXPERIENCE

() ІВМ

QRADAR L2 ENGINEER | 2022 - Present

- Maintain and support the Qradar app framework.
- Bash scripting to automate common tasks.
- I have worked on the development of internal tools to make our day to day easier.
 In these projects I have been able to develop my knowledge about web development.

SYKES

NETWORK SEC ENGINEER | 2020-2022

 Providing technical assistance in a variety of Cisco security networking solutions by handling a variety of tickets addressing customer's concerns about implementation, design, quotes and making sure they meet an appropriate resolution